<?xml version='1.0' standalone='yes'?>
<lesson>
<topic>
	<title>Session Objectives</title>
	<text>
		At the end of this session, you will be able to
			Perform Scandisk
			Perform Disk defragmentation 
			Perform Backup
			Perform Virus Scan
	</text>

	<links>
	<link>//www.youtube.com/embed/1ZI9CVxU2_Y</link>
	</links>
</topic>

<topic>
	<title>Introduction</title>
	<text>Welcome to the session on Connecting Basic Peripheral Devices. This session will teach you how to connect basic peripheral devices and start up a computer system.</text>
<links>
	<link> //www.youtube.com/embed/1ZI9CVxU2_Y </link>
	<link> //www.youtube.com/embed/KULJOEkR0l4 </link>

</links>
</topic>

<topic>
	<title> How to scan a disk for errors </title>
	<text> 
	What is Scandisk? 

		Scandisk is a software utility that comes with the Windows operating system. It detects and corrects errors in the hard disk.

		Procedures

		From the Desktop double click on the My Computer icon.
	</text>
	<links>
	<link>//www.youtube.com/embed/1ZI9CVxU2_Y</link>
	</links>
</topic>
<topic>
	<title>Introduction</title>
	<text>Welcome to the session on Connecting Basic Peripheral Devices. This session will teach you how to connect basic peripheral devices and start up a computer system.</text>
<links>
	<link> //www.youtube.com/embed/1ZI9CVxU2_Y </link>
	<link> //www.youtube.com/embed/KULJOEkR0l4 </link>

</links>
</topic>
<topic>
	<title> How to Back Up Files  </title>
	<text> 
	While hard drives nowadays become very reliable, there is still a chance that they will fail, causing you to lose important files. So its best to back-up  documents, pictures and other data on your hard drive from time to time.
	To back-up a drive is to make a copy of files which and stored these in a seperately location from the original files.
	</text>
	<links>
	<link>//www.youtube.com/embed/1ZI9CVxU2_Y</link>
	</links>
</topic>

<topic>
	<title> How to Scan and Clean Computer Virus  </title>
	<text> 
A computer virus is a computer program that may affect your hard drive seriously. This may spread within your hard drive or from one computer to another computer using a removable device like CD, DVD or USB drive.	
	</text>
	<links>
	<link>//www.youtube.com/embed/1ZI9CVxU2_Y</link>
	</links>
</topic>

 
</lesson>	
